privacy polciy[ubeeadmin](https://www.ubeeinteractive.com/?author=4 "Posts by ubeeadmin")2019-11-27T08:32:24+00:00

Ubee Privacy Policy
-------------------

**INTRODUCTION**

Ubee Interactive Corporation and its global affiliates (“Ubee” or “us” or “we”) value your privacy.    This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect through the websites, how we may use that information, with whom we may share it, and what we do to protect it.

### 1.    THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

We may collect, use, store, and transfer different kinds of Personal Information about you that we have grouped together as follows:

* **Identity Data** includes your name or a similar identifier.
* **Contact Data** includes your physical address, email address, telephone number, and any other information you choose to provide to us in the “Contact Us” form.
* **Applicant Data** includes information that you have provided as part of an inquiry for employment, including your education, employment history, and similar matters.
* **Technical Data** includes internet protocol (IP) address, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.

If you voluntarily provide us with your Personal Information for any purpose, we will process your information in accordance with your request and may retain that information for future opportunities consistent with your request.  Processing of this information is necessary for the purposes of fulfilling your request.

Where you have provided us with Applicant Data, we may use that information in order to allow us to make an informed decision about whether to proceed with your application.  The processing of this information is necessary for the purposes of carrying out the obligations and exercising our rights when deciding whether to recruit you.

### 2.    HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED?

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

* **Direct interactions.** You may give us your Identity and Contact Data by filling in forms or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email, or otherwise. This includes Personal Information you provide when you fill out a “Contact Us” form on the website.  You may give us your Applicant Data if you submit such information to us in connection with your application to be considered for a particular job position.
* **Automated technologies or interactions.** As you interact with our website, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns.

It is important that the Personal Information we hold about you is accurate and current.  Please keep us informed if your Personal Information changes during your relationship with us.  You may provide updates and changes by contacting us using the Contact Us section.  California residents should read our California Privacy Rights section below, and European residents should read our EU Privacy Rights section below.

### 3.    HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

#### **Purposes for Which We Will Use Your Personal Information**

Our primary purpose for collecting Personal Information is to provide you with products and services you request.  Most commonly, we will use your Personal Information in the following circumstances:

* to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you
* To provide you with the information, products, or services you requested
* To process transactions you have requested or agreed to receive, including to send you newsletters, marketing materials, and promotional offers
* To contact you with regard to your use of the website and/or any of our services and, in our discretion, changes to the website, services, and/or any company policies
* As we believe necessary or appropriate, including:
    * under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence;
    * to comply with legal process;
    * to enforce our terms and conditions;
    * To protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others

We may process your Personal Information for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data.

**Affiliates**

Information we collect from you may be shared with our affiliates.

**Business Transfers**

Information we collect from you may be transferred to another company as part of a merger or acquisition by that company.

**Change of Purpose**

We will only use your Personal Information for the purposes for which we collected it.  Please note that we may process your Personal Information without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.

### 4.    DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Ubee does not sell Personal Information.  However, we may share your Personal Information for the following purposes and pursuant to the following legal bases

* to respond to your inquiries or requests, the legal basis of such processing being your consent;
* to process your job application information, the legal basis of such processing being your consent; and
* Subject to applicable law, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process, such as a subpoena; (ii) in response to requests by government entities, such as law enforcement authorities; (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical, financial or other harm, injury, or loss; or (iv) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity.

The above does not affect your legal rights under the relevant data protection legislation of your country.

### 5.    HOW LONG DO WE RETAIN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We will only retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of responding your request, satisfying any legal obligations, accounting, enforce our agreement or reporting requirements.  We will dispose personal data within a reasonable time after it is no longer necessary for the business purpose for which it was collected.

### 6.    YOUR CHOICE

**Opt Out**

You may also withdraw consent to the collection and use of your personal data, to the extent that we are relying on such consent to process your data.  You can exercise the right to opt out by contacting us at [urprivacy@ubeeinteractive.com](mailto:urprivacy@ubeeinteractive.com).

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents who have provided personally identifiable information to us, if any, to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.  We do not share information we collect about you with third parties for those third-parties’ direct marketing purposes.  Upon verification of your identity you may:

* Request disclosure of the following information :
    * Categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year.
    * The names and addresses of third parties that received such personal information.
    * Business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling personal information.
* Request access to certain personal information we have collected.
* Request deletion of your personal information, subject to the exceptions provided by law.

You are entitled to receive a copy of this information up to one request per calendar year in a standardized format and the information will not be specific to you individually.  Request can be submitted at [urprivacy@ubeeinteractive.com](mailto:urprivacy@ubeeinteractive.com).  We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted to addresses other than the addresses specified in this paragraph. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response.  Please allow up to forty-five (45) days for a response.

**Your European Privacy Rights**

If you are located in the EU and you utilize our website, or if we collect, track and/or process or transfer Personal Information from you, or Personal Information which you submit to us through the website, your data will be managed in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your Personal Information.  Request can be submitted at [urprivacy@ubeeinteractive.com](mailto:urprivacy@ubeeinteractive.com).  You have the right to:

* Request access to certain personal data records we hold about you (a data subject access request) (including receiving this as an electronic copy).
* Update and correct any incomplete or inaccurate personal data we hold about you.
* Request erasure of your personal data, subject to the exceptions provided by law.
* Request restriction of the processing of your personal information, under certain conditions.
* Object to the processing of your personal information, under certain conditions.
* Request the transfer of your personal data to you or another organization, under certain conditions.
* Lodge a complaint with the local data protection authority.

### 7.    INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA

We are part of a global group of companies and share infrastructure and functions across our businesses internationally.  By using the website and/or our services you consent to the transfer of your personal data to third party data processors outside the EU.  We may transfer your information to other countries, including those outside the EU, either for storage purposes or if we engage suppliers, or third-party data processors.  We endeavor to comply with the applicable EU data protection laws as regards such direct collection and further processing of personal data originating from the EU.

### 8.    CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our website is intended for adults. We do not intentionally or knowingly collect personally-identifiable information from children as defined by applicable law and we request that children not submit any personal data to us.

### 9.    CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY NOTICE

We may change this privacy Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically.  When you visit our websites or use our services, you are accepting the current version of this Privacy Policy.  If we change the Privacy Policy in a material way, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change.

### 10.  CONTACT DETAIL

For questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [urprivacy@ubeeinteractive.com](mailto:urprivacy@ubeeinteractive.com).

© Ubee Interactive. All rights reserved. | [Privacy Policy](http://www.ubeeinteractive.com/?page_id=21183)
